This meat's so good!
It's so tender!
Is the one you've got there Breakfast Set B?
Nope, Set C.
That one was good, too...
A through E were all delicious!
What do you think, Chris?
I'm going to start over with A again.
Of course, so will I.
Crap! Crap! I overslept!
You were supposed to wake me up, Rati!
Why did you oversleep?
Thanks to you, I overslept too!
Have your roommate wake you up!
I told them they didn't have to,
because you were going to do it!
Well, that's your problem.
How much are you lot eating for breakfast?!
The three of you ate all this?
No, I just had this one plate.
So the two of you ate all this?
Isn't that too much food for breakfast?
It's normal, isn't it, Chris?
Breakfast is the most
important meal of the day.
We need the energy to get us
through the day ahead!
No, you've already eaten
enough for three days.
You were amazing yesterday!
You beat those three golems by yourself!
Thanks.
Hey, don't push me!
I'm not pushing you.
I'm Rati, from the squire program.
This is Pram, from the knights.
Hi, I'm Pram.
Nice to meet you.
I'm Rafinha, from the knights.
I'm Inglis, from the squires.
Nice to meet you!
Leone, from the knights. Hi.
Whisper, whisper, whisper, whisper.
I think people are staring.
Oh, that's because of me...
A-Ah. Well, I'm not from this country,
so that stuff doesn't mean much to me.
Where are you from?
Alucard. Same as Pram.
So you're exchange students.
Yeah. This place is nice and warm...
Rati, we have to finish eating!
Class is gonna start!
Oops, sorry!
Pram, let's hurry up and order!
We'll go with you.
Let's get extra-large portions!
You're still eating?!
Reborn
to Master the Blade
From Hero-King to Extraordinary Squire
Episode 6     Labyrinth of Trials
I'm Margoose, the practical
instructor for you freshmen!
Today we'll be doing a Flying Gear
exercise with both the knights and squires.
I want to start by making one thing clear:
Our war isn't just against
the magicite beasts!
We war against ourselves,
pushing ourselves to the limit
to bring peace and safety to the people!
And that starts with training our bodies!
So we're all going to run
to the Flying Gear dock!
And the Flying Gears are already
out of the equation.
Get moving! Double time!
He's fast! I'm already losing sight of him!
Where's the Flying Gear dock?
I saw it yesterday. It's pretty far.
We need to keep up with him!
This is a nice change of pace.
But just running there normally
wouldn't be any fun at all.
I'll try that gravity effect that
Principal Miliera used yesterday.
First, I convert my aether to mana...
And then, the way she set up her mana was...
Okay, that'll do for now.
If I get better,
I bet I can make it heavier!
Seriously? How is she so fast?
Inglis was still standing there
when we left...
Don't worry. Chris is...
See?
Leone, lets pick up the pace.
Huh? Okay!
Rati, wait! Jeez!
Don't hurt yourselves trying to keep up!
You're not expected to match
my speed from the start...
Can I go on ahead?
S-Sure.
What's your name?
Inglis Eucus.
You've got potential!
Very good!
Wait up!
Wow! Not bad!
Damn it! You're not even breaking
a sweat, and I'm dying here!
Looks like this year's
freshmen have potential!
Good, good.
Don't forget me.
W-We managed to catch up...
I don't think Chris is using
her full strength yet.
I'm not gonna lose, even if it kills me!
That's the spirit!
I'll be going on ahead!
How is she doing that?
I told you. She wasn't
using her full strength.
If I tried to catch up to her,
I might actually die.
Wow!
It's kind of exciting to look at,
isn't it, Chris?
It sure is, Rani.
This is the Royal Academy.
It's got the latest technology.
Now, form up into groups.
Two or three to a Flying Gear.
Once it's outside, get on board!
One of you takes the controls.
The others, hang on tight
and make sure you don't fall off!
Can I go first?
Sure!
Squires spend a lot of time
piloting Flying Gears, after all.
Good luck, Inglis!
The instructions for flying it
are on the panel in front of you.
After you activate the engine,
switch it to flight mode.
When the wings on both sides deploy,
slowly bring up the accelerator.
Wow, we're flying!
Keep it up, Chris!
Yeah...
This is gonna work!
This feels so good!
And the scenery's beautiful!
Aren't we going a little too fast?
I'm kind of scared...
But we're going to use these
to fight the magicite beasts, right?
Better get used to it.
That's right!
And this is the best way!
Wow, Rati!
You're really good at this!
Looks like when it comes
to Flying Gears, I win!
I'll catch up to him.
What are you doing?
I hate to lose.
L-Looks like... freshmen... potential!
Good...
Wow, she's amazing.
Not only is she pretty,
the things she does are incredible.
Why are you talking like that
when you've already got me, Rati?
Like what?
You never call me pretty! It's not fair!
Stop it! That's dangerous!
I'm sure you're tired after your classes,
but we've got a special test for you today.
If I call your name, step forward.
A special test....
Rafinha. Liselotte. Leone. Pram.
Yes, ma'am!
Y-Yes, ma'am!
You four are the students that have been
recommended from the knight program.
And also Inglis...
Yes, ma'am.
You've been recommended
from the squire program.
Hey, is that the test that
everyone was talking about?
Yes! It's a huge honor just
to be recommended for it,
since it means the academy
thinks you've got potential!
The test is simple.
I'm going to send you somewhere.
Come back here before the time limit is up.
If you can do that, you pass!
Where is "somewhere"?
A special space created by an Artifact!
We call it the Labyrinth of Trials.
It will test not only your strength,
but your mental fortitude as well.
Mental fortitude...
You might find yourself suffering...
But the goal is to enhance
your mental strength as knights.
Understood?
Yes, ma'am!
You okay?
I won't let you beat me!
She appears to view me as a rival
for some reason, but...
No matter.
Pick a door.
Each of you will find an
appropriate trial beyond it.
Now, let the test begin!
Rani, Leone, be careful!
You too, Chris!
Let's do our best!
I know I can do this!
This is... every foe I've ever fought!
The perfect test!
Here I go!
What?
This isn't a test...
Chris...
Rani?
Memories from my youth?
I just keep going back
through my memories...
No enemies to be seen.
I've returned to when I was newly born.
Is this the end? No...
These are...
memories of my last life?
Your Highness...
That voice...
It's been many years, Your Highness.
Randall...
My heir, and the man who was set
to inherit the kingdom after my death.
If you're really Randall,
I'd like to know why, after I died,
some people in this world started thinking
of themselves as better than others.
But you won't have an answer
for me, will you?
That is correct, Your Majesty!
This isn't good.
If I keep going, I might end up
running into the Goddess Alistia.
This was supposed to be a test of
mental strength? I don't like it.
I've got better things to do
than waste my time here.
There's more up there?
Wh-What was that?
I see!
So it's connected to the spaces
where the others are?
Did you do this?
Yeah. I didn't feel like
continuing straight ahead.
How could she destroy such a strange space?
Just who are you?
Just a simple squire,
in Rafinha Bilford's service.
If you're her squire, tell her not
to hate her classmate so much.
I'm not here to be her enemy.
I don't think she hates you.
She does!
She tries to stay away from me as best
she can and won't look me in the eye!
Then maybe she's upset
with the way you treat Leone.
I'm the daughter of this
kingdom's chancellor.
I need to be careful.
Though, to be honest...
Oh?
I do feel I went a little too far.
Okay. I'll tell her for you.
So, you think we can get out of here?
I'm sick of this place. It just
brings back all my bad memories.
Me too.
So I figured I'd bust my way out.
Want to join me?
That sounds fun.
Let's go together.
Okay, let's go.
Wait.
Is that your Gift?
Yes. I'll take you to the top.
Wow!
You don't even need a Flying Gear!
Stop! What are you doing to my brother?
Move! You're wrong about this!
That's... Leon?
My brother's a holy knight now!
He's an inspiration to everyone!
Why are you being so mean?
It's all a lie!
You'll understand some day!
Curse you! And on the very day
my son became a holy knight!
What are you going to do to Leon?
Mother... Father...
Those wounds... She's already
expended a great deal of her mana.
She must have overcome many
fierce battles to reach this point.
I'll... I'll defeat you
and keep going forward!
I'll defeat my brother Leon!
Go on ahead. I'll help her.
I won't let you take another step forward,
if you're going to hurt my child!
Begone! Go!
I'll protect Leon,
even at the cost of my life!
Begone, traitor!
Sorry to interrupt!
I-Inglis?
I'm glad I made it.
How did you get here?
I broke through the walls.
That's crazy...
That's not how the test is supposed to work.
Nobody said I couldn't!
I won't let you hurt my brother!
I'll protect Leon, no matter what!
Inglis?
I'll handle them.
Y-You're...
It's hard for you or your friends
to fight them, right?
It's easier for me.
Yeah, thanks.
Th-Thank you.
I'd like to apologize for
hurting you the other day.
I'm sorry.
No, it's not...
Liselotte's actually a nice girl, huh?
That "actually" was unnecessary!
Now, let's head for the top floor.
Hurry up!
Wow!
She doesn't even need a Flying Gear, right?
You just said that!
Welcome back.
I guess we made it out.
Yeah.
Huh?
You came out of a different door
than the one you went in!
And the three of you all
came out of the same door?
Nothing really unusual happened.
Really?
That's a huge lie.
Maybe it's broken...
You two helped me on the way, too...
You don't want to do it
all over again, right?
Principal Miliera,
this means we passed, right?
Well, you did come out of the door.
So I guess I have to pass you.
You pass. Congratulations!
Where are Rani and Pram?
Oh, did she pass already?
No, she failed almost immediately.
A hole opened, and she got tossed out.
I was supposed to win this!
I told you to give it up.
Rani!
Chris!
I finally made it out!
Rafinha, you pass!
Welcome back, Rani!
Congratulations!
Thank you!
You two both passed, right?
Huh? Oh, of course.
I guess...
You guess?
Never mind.
Anyway, were you okay?
I'm so tired!
I'm gonna eat a lot and then sleep!
When you're tired, you move
around in your sleep a lot.
It's going to be a rough night.
That's so mean, Chris!
S-Sorry, it's my fault...
No! No! That's not what I meant!
If that's what this is about...
You gonna be okay, Leone?
I-I'm fine.
It'll be fine.
Liselotte's actually a good girl.
Yeah, I know.
Why are you standing outside
my room and talking about me?
Welcome to our room!
Th-Thanks for having me.
Now, come inside.
Hey...
I was just kidding.
Liselotte can be surprisingly silly.
I'd prefer you said I had a sense of humor.
Wow, this room is so cute!
This isn't the furniture
that came with the room!
I brought in the same kind I have at home!
Hey, I brought a lot of party things
so we could have a celebration!
A celebration of what?
You know... making up... and stuff.
I brought lots of food, too!
You've still got room for food
after all you ate at dinner?!
m 0 0 l 100 0 100 100 0 100
Leone's
fashion sense
is surprisingly
bold...
m 0 0 l 100 0 100 100 0 100
*Especially around
the chest
Oh, my!
Comic by Kuromura Moto